Topical files 2
Marist Archives and Special Collections
- Topical files 2, 2.1.9.5
  - Harold Salisbury, 1966; 23 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of First letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of Second letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 4
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of Second letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 5
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 3 of Second letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 6
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 4 of Second letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 7
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 5 of Second letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 8
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 6 of Second letter to Lowell Thomas from Harold Salisbury], 9
  - John R. Samuelson [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1952; 24 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from John R. Samuelson], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from John R. Samuelson], 2
    - [John R. Samuelson:][Portrait of L.T. with picture of Washington Monument], 3
  - John Sandison [color photographs], 1979; 25 (Box 1618)
    - [John Sandison:]J. S., Patti Sandison, Debbie Boone, Pat Boone, 1
    - Verso: J. S., Patti Sandison, Debbie Boone, Pat Boone, 1-verso
    - [John Sandison:]Bob Hope, J. S., 2
    - Verso: Bob Hope, J. S., 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from John Sandison], 3
  - Albert Sarber [color photograph], 1972; 26 (Box 1618)
    - [Albert Sarber (color photo): A book on Lowell Thomas and a photo of Lowell Thomas sitting on an end table], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter and newspaper clipping sent to L.T. from Albert F. Sarber], 2
  - A. Schaefflin, 1968; 27 (Box 1618)
    - [Postcard] July 28/68 Dear Lowell- Spending 10 days in MK walking the Giant Area. Hope we can ski the great Bowls together next winter. Very Best Wishes, A[?] Schaefflin, 1
    - Verso: July 28/68 Dear Lowell- Spending 10 days in MK walking the Giant Area. Hope we can ski the great Bowls together next winter. Very Best Wishes, A[?] Schaefflin, 1-verso
  - Albert Schenlin, 1957; 28 (Box 1618)
    - [Albert Schenlin: Dog sitting in yard][Feb 1954], 1
    - Verso: Feb 1954, 1-verso
  - A. H. Scott, 1944; 29 (Box 1618)
    - Mr. + Mrs. A.H. Scott of Coleraine, Minn., with part of their Doll hobby - dolls that they make, and dress in costumes of people of other countries, 1
    - Verso: Mr. + Mrs. A.H. Scott of Coleraine, Minn., with part of their Doll hobby - dolls that they make, and dress in costumes of people of other countries, 1-verso
  - Henry L. Scott Concerts, 1953; 30 (Box 1618)
    - [Henry L. Scott Concerts: Body of water and hills], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Henry L. Scott], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Henry L. Scott], 3
  - Harrison L. Scullion, 1964; 31 (Box 1618)
    - [Harrison L. Scullion: (written)]picture at right Turkish German + Austrian medal with from Cross Sphinx Tuskish Star + Cresent rising sun German field gun desert oldest ruins in the world at Ballbeck Syria under pillars is sacred [?] of Egypt Turkish German + Austrian coat of arms + 1916, 1
    - Verso: picture at right Turkish German + Austrian medal with from Cross Sphinx Tuskish Star + Cresent rising sun German field gun desert oldest ruins in the world at Ballbeck Syria under pillars is sacred [?] of Egypt Turkish German + Austrian coat of arms + 1916, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Harrison L. Scullion], 2
  - Ed Seiler [color photographs], 1968 - circa 1971; 32 (Box 1618)
    - [Ed Seiler (color photo): Body of water, pine trees, snowcapped mountains], 1
    - [Ed Seiler (color photo): Body of water, pine trees, snowcapped mountains], 2
    - Aerial view of Enchanted Lake Lodge from the northwest (showing the main building and guest house. The road leads downhill to the plane dock and guarters for the help.) E.W. Seiler, 3
    - Verso: Aerial view of Enchanted Lake Lodge from the northwest (showing the main building and guest house. The road leads downhill to the plane dock and guarters for the help.) E.W. Seiler, 3-verso
  - Bob Sheehan [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], undated; 33 (Box 1618)
    - [Bob Sheehan and Lowell Thomas], 1
    - Note: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Bob Sheehan], 2
  - Sasha Siemel, 1950; 34 (Box 1618)
    - [Jaguar] Dear Lowell, We again returned to the land of the big pussy-cats, but this time we intend to capture as many as possible alife and bring them back to U.S. Zoos next spring. Sincerely, Sasha Siemel, 1
    - Verso: Dear Lowell, We again returned to the land of the big pussy-cats, but this time we intend to capture as many as possible alife and bring them back to U.S. Zoos next spring. Sincerely, Sasha Siemel, 1-verso
  - Edith and Howard Smith, 1961; 35 (Box 1618)
    - [Edith and Howard Smith], 1
  - Harry L. Smith [plane crash photographs], 1975 March; 36 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Harry L. Smith], 1
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 2
    - [Harry L. Smith: People standing by wrecked airplane], 3
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 4
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 5
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 6
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 7
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 8
    - [Harry L. Smith: Wrecked airplane], 9
  - Frank Springer-Miller, 1956; 37 (Box 1618)
    - Conveyed your hello to [?] who sends regards. Am making a tour of a half-dozen resorts. So far only fun, spring skiing, but suddenly cold today. Going to [?] Valley next, it looks like they are getting the [?] for 1960alright. Best Regards, Frank Springer-Miller, 1
    - Verso[PDF]: Conveyed your hello to [?] who sends regards. Am making a tour of a half-dozen resorts. So far only fun, spring skiing, but suddenly cold today. Going to [?] Valley next, it looks like they are getting the [?] for 1960alright. Best Regards, Frank Springer-Miller, 1-verso
  - Glen M. Stadler, circa 1973; 38 (Box 1618)
    - No - This isn't me, but ut us my station. When do you plan to visit these parts?, 1
    - Verso: No - This isn't me, but ut us my station. When do you plan to visit these parts?, 1-verso
  - Joanie Stadler [color photograph], 1980; 39 (Box 1618)
    - Caption: The Stadlers have gone hog wild in wishing you a Happy Valentine's Day; Verso: Happiness is over a week of Colorado skiing - with only bruises! We were in Vail with old friends&, 1
    - Verso[PDF]: Happiness is over a week of Colorado skiing - with only bruises! We were in Vail with old friends&, 1-verso
  - Yvonne H. Stevenson, 1964; 40 (Box 1618)
    - [Yvonne H. Stevenson: Woman looking at papers], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Yvonne H. Stevenson], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Yvonne H. Stevenson], 3
  - A. E. Strecker [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1952; 41 (Box 1618)
    - [A.E. Strecker:]From left to right: Maj. Howell, Maj Wible, Capt Crowley, Lt. Willon, Capt. Bradley, Lt. Michels, unidentified O.W.I. Man, Capt Leigh, Capt. Sandborn, Capt. Ruder. Maj. Strecker, and Lowell Thomas. Hotel Miramar Fedela. Fr. M. North Africa Apr-May 1945, 1
    - Verso: From left to right: Maj. Howell, Maj Wible, Capt Crowley, Lt. Willon, Capt. Bradley, Lt. Michels, unidentified O.W.I. Man, Capt Leigh, Capt. Sandborn, Capt. Ruder. Maj. Strecker, and Lowell Thomas. Hotel Miramar Fedela. Fr. M. North Africa Apr-May 1945, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from A. T. [E.?] Strecker], 2
  - Kenneth Strumm [color photograph], 1978; 42 (Box 1618)
    - [Kenneth Strumm (color photo): Framed picture of ship on water], 1
  - Mrs. John J. Sweeney, 1945; 43 (Box 1618)
    - [Mrs. John J. Sweeney:]Jack 11/19/43; F/O John J. Sweeney, Jr. T-7370. 7701 West Chester Pike Upper Darby, Pa., 1
    - Verso: Jack 11/19/43; F/O John J. Sweeney, Jr. T-7370. 7701 West Chester Pike Upper Darby, Pa., 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: Mrs. John J. Sweeney: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Anne C. Sweeney], 2
    - Note[PDF]: Mrs. John J. Sweeney: [Page 2-3 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Anne C. Sweeney], 3
    - Note[PDF]: Mrs. John J. Sweeney: [Page 4 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Anne C. Sweeney], 4
  - S - Miscellaneous, circa 1938; 44 (Box 1618)
    - [S -Miscellaneous:]Caption: Butch [Boy sitting on bench, reading], 1
  - Nick J. Terzakis [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1949; 45 (Box 1618)
    - Nick proudly present the newly king of air crator Mr Thomas Lowell stanging [standing] in the Royal car of Queen Marie Prince Paul, Prince Carl and King Peter, Princess T Brahim of Cairo. This snap took place at Drake- Hotel photo by Nick J. Terzakis official April 1949, 1
    - Verso: Nick proudly present the newly king of air crator Mr Thomas Lowell stanging [standing] in the Royal car of Queen Marie Prince Paul, Prince Carl and King Peter, Princess T Brahim of Cairo. This snap took place at Drake- Hotel photo by Nick J. Terzakis official April 1949, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: Nick J. Terzakis: [back of postcard and envelope], 2
    - Note[PDF]: Nick J. Terzakis: [front of postcard and back of envelope], 3
  - Tey Manufacturing Corporation, 1950; 46 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: Tey Manufacturing Corporation: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Art Hunt], 1
    - Tey Manufacturing Corporation: My two children, Judy and Artie, playing in the snow., 2
    - Note: Tey Manufacturing Corporation: My two children, Judy and Artie, playing in the snow., 3
    - Tey Manufacturing Corporation: Skiis Taken with flashbulb soon after the maching was turned on., 4
    - Note: Tey Manufacturing Corporation: Taken with flashbulb soon after the maching was turned on., 5
    - Tey Manufacturing Corporation: Taken after few hours of running., 6
    - Note: Tey Manufacturing Corporation: Taken after few hours of running., 7
  - Earl M. Thacker [color photograph], 1957; 47 (Box 1618)
    - Directions & mileage to Earl Thacker & Dickey Thacker's, Diamond T-Bar Ranch on Koko Crater-Oahu, Hawaii, 1
    - Verso: Directions & mileage to Earl Thacker & Dickey Thacker's, Diamond T-Bar Ranch on Koko Crater-Oahu, Hawaii, 1-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Earl M. Thacker], 2
  - Henry A. Thomas [color photographs], circa 1975; 48 (Box 1618)
    - [Henry A. Thomas (color photo):]For Mr T. This is my new house. And the new car in the front, The Swimming Pool in the Rear. 3 Bedrooms, 2 stone Rooms, closets galore - HAT, 1
    - Verso: For Mr T. This is my new house. And the new car in the front, The Swimming Pool in the Rear. 3 Bedrooms, 2 stone Rooms, closets galore - HAT, 1-verso
    - [Henry A. Thomas (color photo):]This is even better then my retreat at Lake g[G]regory 30 miles from here - HAT 12-11-74 [House], 2
    - Verso: This is even better then my retreat at Lake gregory 30 miles from here - HAT 12-11-74, 2-verso
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from H. A. Thomas], 3
    - Note[PDF]: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from H. A. Thomas], 4
  - Captain L. R. Thomas [color photograph], circa 1970; 49 (Box 1618)
    - [Captain L.R. Thomas (color photo):]Caption: Seasons Greetings from Okinawa; Tamara, Lowell II, Lowell + Lynn Thomas, 1
    - Note: [address] Cpt. & Mrs. L. R. Thomas, 2
  - Raymond Thornburg, 1961; 50 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from Raymond Thornberg [Thornburg?]], 1
    - [Raymond Thornburg: Portrait of a man in glasses (Raymond Thornburg?)], 2
  - David H. Tilley, 1978; 51 (Box 1618)
    - [David H. Tilley:]Home in Victor, Colorado, 1959, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from David. H. Tilley], 2
  - Ina and Sandy Treat [color photograph], circa 1979; 52 (Box 1618)
    - [Ina and Sandy Treat (color photo): Man holding a framed painting], 1
    - Note[PDF]: Ina and Sandy Treat: [Page 1 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Sandy Treat, Sr.], 2
    - Note[PDF]: Ina and Sandy Treat: [Page 2 of letter to Lowell Thomas from Sandy Treat, Sr.], 3
  - The Treats [color photograph], 1968; 53 (Box 1618)
    - Caption: Merry Christmas - Happy New Year - The Treats, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from the Treats], 2
  - J. David Truby, 1973; 54 (Box 1618)
    - [J. David Truby:]Caption: Ground Lewis gun [Man holding a gun], 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from J. David Truby], 2
  - Tyree [color photograph], circa 1980; 55 (Box 1618)
    - [Tyree (color photo):][photography that was attached to card], 1
    - [Tyree (color photo)]Note: Merry Christmas and Happy New Year!, 2
  - T - Miscellaneous, circa 1950; 56 (Box 1618)
    - [T -miscellaneous:]Greetings! [?] and Happy Returns, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [T -miscellaneous:] [Page 1 of 2] Greetings! [?] and Happy Returns [Chrystine and Dick Trace?], 2
    - Note[PDF]: [T -miscellaneous:] [Page 2 of 2] Greetings! [?] and Happy Returns [Chrystine and Dick Trace?], 3
  - James Van Nierkerk, circa 1965; 57 (Box 1618)
    - [James Van Nierkerk: Man holding a shot crocodile:]This croc was just shot, 1
    - Verso: This croc was just shot, 1-verso
  - Char Vincent [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas] [color photograph], 1957; 58 (Box 1618)
    - [Char Vicnent (color photo): Three men sitting on a boat on land, Lowell Thomas center][Lowe] &ll Thomas; &ndro Limey; Canaima Lake 10/5/59, 1
    - Verso: [Lowe] &ll Thomas; &ndro Limey; Canaima Lake 10/5/59, 1-verso
    - Char. Vincent, 2
    - Verso: Char. Vincent, 2-verso
  - Allen Wallis [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1972; 59 (Box 1618)
    - [Allen Wallis:]Lowell Thomas with a couple of his renegade pals, 1
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from W. Allen Wallis, Chancellor of The University of Rochester], 2
  - Charles Perry Weimar [color photograph], 1978; 60 (Box 1618)
    - [Charles Perry Wiemar:]Dear Lowell: Don't hear much of you lately. Wrote a month or so back and informed you of my double pneumonia and it's results and Marcia's Double Pass. And this January. She fell on white decerative stine at a Dog Hospital and broke her hip&, 1
    - Verso: Dear Lowell: Don't hear much of you lately. Wrote a month or so back and informed you of my double pneumonia and it's results and Marcia's Double Pass. And this January. She fell on white decerative stine at a Dog Hospital and broke her hip&, 1-verso
    - [Charles Perry Wiemar:]Note: [envelope], 2
  - Elbert and Uma Wickes [color photograph], 1975; 61 (Box 1618)
    - Caption: Merry Christmas, Our house to your house; Elbert and Una Wickes, 1
    - Verso: Christmas, 1974, 2
  - C. Bruce Wright [includes photograph of Lowell Thomas], 1970; 62 (Box 1618)
    - Note[PDF]: [letter to Lowell Thomas from C. Bruce Wright], 1
    - [C. Bruce Wright: Crowd of people], 2
  - Takashi Yoshimoto, 1962; 63 (Box 1618)
    - [Takashi Yoshimoto], 1